bedida.com 2012-02-02

# The Place to Sell Buy Bid Handmade Products

Privacy 

**Privacy**

Bedida.com is committed to protecting the confidentiality of your personal information. When you register for Bedida.com, we ask only for the information required to meet your needs. By using Bedida.com services, you are voluntarily providing this information to us.

**Your Personal Information**

When you register for Bedida.com, you are voluntarily providing us with personal information such as your name, email address, and some other information.

Bedida.com will not sell your personal information to other companies or organizations. In order to safeguard your personal information, we will use and disclose your personal information only as follows:

  * We may use your information for our internal operations and for any other purpose permitted or required by applicable law. Your personal information will only be accessible by employees and agents who require such information to perform a necessary internal business function for Bedida com.
  * We may use your information to send you communications that are relevant to the services we provide. Unless required, we will not include any of your personal information in the communications other than your email address.
  * We reserve the right to use your personal information to generate aggregate data (summarized data that does not identify you) to perform statistical analyses of the traffic patterns, site usage and behaviors associated with our website.

In certain circumstances, Bedida.com may be legally compelled to release your personal information in response to a court order, subpoena, search warrant, law or regulation. Under these circumstances, we will notify you unless doing so would violate the law or court order.

If you become aware of any unauthorized disclosure of your information, please contact us immediately.

**Your Non-Personal Information**

When you visit our website, we may collect non-personal information from you, such as the internet browser or computer operating system you are using. We use this information only to provide you with better service and improve our website. We will not sell or disclose non-personal information to other companies or organizations.

**Security**

Bedida.com is committed to safeguarding data, computer files and documents containing your personal information from misuse by third parties. 

Bedida.com shall destroy, erase or make unreadable data, computer files and documents containing your personal information prior to disposal.

Sale or Transfer of Information in the Event of Merger, Sale or Bankruptcy

In the event Bedida.com is acquired, merges with another entity, reorganizes, becomes insolvent and/or declares bankruptcy, the website and any information obtained through it may be transferred or sold to another entity, in accordance with applicable law.

**Email Privacy**

You can choose to receive email from Bedida.com on service related topics and promotions. You may also use our website to send an email inquiry to Bedida.com which may result in a reply being sent to an email address that you provide. Responses sent from Bedida.com to your email provider may not be secure or may be intercepted by third parties. By using the email service, you accept the risk of transmitting information from us to your personal email address in an insecure environment.

If you are receiving email correspondence at an employer's email address, please note that, under law, the employer may be permitted to view the contents of any email messages received at this address.

**Usage by Children**

Bedida.com is not intended nor designed to attract users who are minor children. We have no intention of collecting personal information from minor children. Minor children under the age of 18 may only use this website with the prior express consent of a parent or legal guardian and then only under their direct supervision.

**Cookies**

When you visit our website, we may store information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar file and will be used to determine ways to improve our website and services. With most internet browsers, you can erase cookies from your hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. You should refer to your internet browser’s instructions to learn more about these functions. Bedida.com does not use cookies to create profiles that track the viewing preferences of our users.

**Links to Other Sites**

Bedida.com may include links to other sites that are not related to, or are not the property of, Bedida Inc. We are not responsible for the dependability or security of these other sites.

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**

Bedida.com reserves the right at its discretion to change, modify, add or remove portions of this policy or any of its supplemental policies at any time. We will communicate any updates to our policy on the website for any website visitors.
